

NỀN TẢNG TUYỂN DỤNG NHÂN SỰ HÀNG ĐẦU VIỆT NAM

Úng viên HUYNH duc duy | Nguồn tuyendung.topcv.vn





HUYNH DUC DUY

NOC IT ENGINEER

- 12/03/1999
- Male
- 0944574683
- duyhuynh0399@gmail.com
- 🕋 District 5, Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam
- linkedin.com/in/huỳnh-đức-duya48 b561b3

OBJECTIVE

With my knowledge and experience in networking, I always try to hone my knowledge and gain experience to improve myself. I want to become a member in a professional environment, so that I have the opportunity to devote myself and have the opportunity to advance in my career, develop in the field of Network Infrastructure Administration and Security.

EDUCATION

2017 - 2022

UNIVERSITY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY - VIET NAM NATIONAL UNIVERSITY HO CHI MINH CITY | Major: INFORMATION SECURITY

JUN 2020 - SEP 2020

CERTIFIED NETWORK SECURITY CENTER (CNSC) | CCNA COURSE

MAR 2021 - JUL 2021

GRADUATION THESIS | Research on NFV-based Virtual Network Function and Service Function Chain

Research Contents

- Traditional network infrastructure
- Network functions used in the network system
- Network Function Virtualization (NFV)
- Virtual Network Function (VNF)
- Service Function Chaining (SFC)
- Software-Defined Networking (SDN)
- Openstack
- Open-Source Management and Orchesstration (MANO) OSM
- Python, YAML, JSON

WORK EXPERIENCE

SEP 2020 - DEC 2020

LIEN PHAT TECHNOLOGY CORPORATION (LPC) | Technical Internship

Learn and familiarize myself with the processes and ways of working in the corporate environment. Research on SDN and contact many network devices under the supervision and guidance of the leader of the Network & Security team.

NOV 2021 - FEB 2023

LIEN PHAT TECHNOLOGY CORPORATION (LPC) | Technical Staff

- Deployment of network and system related projects
- Checking and delivering information technology goods to customers
- Support customers to operate, fix errors, handle problems during and after deployment
- Support network optimization projects and service contracts

CERTIFICATIONS

DEC 2021

TOEIC LISTENING & READING TOTAL SCORE 610

FEB 2022

FORTINET NSE 1

FEB 2022

FORTINET NSE 2

MAR 2022

FORTINET NSE 3

JUN 2022

CISCO CERTIFIED NETWORK ASSOCIATE (CCNA)



PROJECTS

Deploying network systems using Cisco switches and firewalls Sophos, Draytek

Deploying Wifi systems using Access Points of Ruckus, Aruba, Unifi, Cambium

Support troubleshooting for users

Integrating Sophos, Fortinet firewall devices into the system

Periodic maintenance of network infrastructure (Cisco Switchs, Cisco Access Points)

Support customers in monitoring and troubleshooting while operating network infrastructure